Finding Aid for William Albright Papers 1962-1998
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Scores
  - Various Composers
    - Phipps, Karen (student)
      - My Grace is Sufficient for choir and organ, copyright, 1991 (Box 41)
      - Psalm 139: Choir, cello and organ, copyright, 1993 (Box 41)
      - When in Our Music God is Glorified: A Hymn Concertato for Congregation, SATB Choir, Children, optional Flute and Trumpets, undated (Box 41)
      - Wilderness Lake for Wind Ensemble, copyright, 1991 (Box 41)
    - Place, David (student)
      - Ganymede: A Concerto for Traverso and Baroque Orchestra, copyright, 1982 (Box 41)
    - Plain, George
      - Antics: A Collection of Songs for Soprano with Piano Accompaniment (poems by Eugene Walter), 1990 (Box 41)
      - And left ol' Joe a bone, AMAZING! for orchestra, 1975 (Box 52)
      - My Dog for SATB chorus (poem by Anthony Oldnknow), 1978 (Box 41)
      - Portrait I: Sally Goodin for flute, violin, violoncello and harp, 1986 (Box 58)
      - Raccoon Song for cello, 1973 (Box 41)
    - Powell, Mel
      - Haiku Settings for voice and piano, 1961 (Box 41)
    - Proudian, John
      - Armenian Songs for baritone, violin, and piano (poems by Hovhannes Toumamian), undated (Box 41)
      - Day's Poems for Lyric Soprano and Piano (poems by Emily Dickinson, Christina Rossetti, and Heather Teeter), undated (Box 41)
      - Duo for Bassoon and Cello, undated (Box 41)
      - Duo for Viola and Suspended Cymbal, undated (Box 41)
    - Putz, Kevin (student)
      - Five Preludes for piano, 1988 (Box 41)
    - Radzynski, Jan
      - David: A Symphony in One Movement, 1987 (Box 41)
      - Time's Other Beat for orchestra, 1990 (Box 41)
    - Reese, Luke (student)
      - Cthonian Lurker for large wind ensemble, 1991 (Box 41)
      - Fantasia for organ, 1992 (Box 41)
      - The Passion of Doctor Voke: Tragic Opera in One Act (libretto by Thomas Ligotti), 1992 (Box 41)
      - Prelude for Orchestra, 1990 (Box 41)
      - Sailing to Byzantium for SSATB chorus (poem by W.B. Yeats), copyright, 1991 (Box 41)
      - Three Idylls: For high voice and piano, 1989 (Box 41)
      - Three Motets for mixed chorus and organ, 1992 (Box 41)
    - Rochberg, George (teacher)
      - Prelude (on Happy Birthday) for almost 2 pianos, undated (Box 41)
      - Songs of Inanna and Dumuzi for Contralto and Piano, copyright, 1983 (Box 41)
      - Variations on an Original Theme for Piano Solo, 1941 (Box 41)
    - Rodgers, L
      - Concert Bal, Tous Les Soirs for clarinet, horn, cello and tack piano, 1972 (Box 42)
    - Ross, William James (friend)
      - Always before your voice my soul: Song for Tenor Solo, Flute, Oboe, Clarinet, Bassoon, Vibraphone, and Violin (text by E.E. Cummings), 1986 (Box 42)
      - A Garland of Alleluias: Double Canon of Celebration for SATB Chorus, Keyboard, and Percussion Instruments, 1994 (Box 42)
      - Holy is This Place: Congregational Introit for Worship with Piano Accompaniment, copyright, 1995 (Box 42)
      - Missa Brevis for voices and organ, copyright, 1978 (Box 42)
      - My God, my God, why have you abandoned me? Responsorial Psalm for Passion Sunday (Palm Sunday) for SATB Cantors or Choir, Solo Oboe, and Organ, with Congregational Response, 1990 (Box 42)
      - Prelude for Piano, 1962 (Box 42)
      - Seasons: Four Fantasy Pieces of Time and the Spirit for Solo Harpsichord 1993 (Box 42)
      - Sonata for flute, violin, and harpsichord, copyright, 1978 (Box 42)
      - Sun Traces: Organ Trio, 1971 (Box 42)
      - Wind Quintet No. 2, copyright, 1990 (Box 42)
    - Roumain, Daniel Bernard (student)
      - Hip-Hop Essay: For Orchestra, 1995 (Box 52)
    - Rouse, Christopher
      - The Dream of Christophene for soprano voice, alto flute, bassoon, horn, percussion, piano, violin, violoncello, and contrabass, 1977 (Box 42)
      - Mitternachtlieder for orchestra, 1979 (Box 42)
      - Second Stratum of Empyrean for solo piano, 1978 (Box 42)
      - String Quartet, 1982 (Box 58)
      - Third Stratum of Empyrean for two choruses and recording, 1979 (Box 42)
    - Rouse, Robert Steven (student)
      - The Avatar for Trumpet and Piano, copyright, 1991 (Box 42)
      - ' Bone To Be Wild for Trombone and Piano, copyright, 1993 (Box 42)
      - Diamonds: Violin Solo, 1989 (Box 42)
      - Flash Point: Etude for Woodwind Quartet, copyright, 1984 (Box 42)
      - Into the Light for Orchestra, copyright, 1991 (Box 42)
      - Light Fantastic for Orchestra, 1994 (Box 42)
      - Psalm 70 for Chorus and Piano, copyright, 1992 (Box 42)
      - Ribbons for String Orchestra, 1991 (Box 42)
      - Short Stories for Orchestra, copyright, 1990 (Box 42)
      - Symphony: Light Descending 1987 (Box 42)
    - Ruders, Poul
      - Corpus Cum Figuris for orchestra, 1984 (Box 53)
    - Ruehr, Elena (student)
      - Vocalissimus for Chamber Orchestra, undated (Box 42)
      - Of Water and Clouds for flute and piano, 1986 (Box 42)
    - Rummel, Jack
      - Nine Contemporary Rags, 1979-1989 (Box 42)
      - Nine More Contemporary Rags, 1982-1991 (Box 42)
    - Rush, Loren
      - Dans le sable, 1968 (Box 58)
      - Mandala Music: Improvisation for three or more performers, undated (Box 42)
      - Oh, Susanna pour piano, 1970 (Box 42)
    - Rush, Steve (student)
      - Call To God for Organ, 1984 (Box 42)
      - Esperanza (Hope) for solo piano, 1993 (Box 42)
        includes note from composer)
    - Sandler, Felicia A.B.
      - Regina Caeli: SSaatTBB A Capella, copyright, 1998 (Box 43)
    - Santos, Erik (student)
      - Air Chunks for solo piano, 1991 (Box 43)
      - Guernica Dances...for two pianos, 1995 (Box 58)
        (signed by composer, includes note from composer
      - Symphony No. 1--Shards 1995 (Box 43)
    - Scavarda, Donald
      - Groups for Piano, 1959 (Box 43)
      - Sounds for Eleven for orchestra, 1961 (Box 53)
    - Schiff, David
      - Scenes from Adolescence for Flute/Piccolo, Clarinet (Bb, Eb), Violin, Cello and Piano, 1987 (Box 43)
    - Schober, David
      - Impure Elements for orchestra, 1998 (Box 53)
    - Schwantner, Joseph
      - And the mountains rising nowhere, 1977 (Box 53)
      - Sparrows for soprano, flute (piccolo), clarinet, violin, viola, cello, piano, harp and percussion (poem by Issa), 1979 (Box 53)
    - Schwartz, Elliott (friend)
      - Areas: Music for Dancers for flute, clarinet, violin, cello, trombone, percussion, dancers and piano, 1968 (Box 43)
      - Eclipse: enigma Variations for Ten Players for 2 clarinets, 2 bassoons, trumpet, trombone, violin, cello, percussion and keyboard, 1971 (Box 43)
      - Four American Portraits, 1985 (Box 43)
      - Four Studies for Two Clarinets, 1964 (Box 43)
      - Interruptions for woodwind quintet, 1965 (Box 43)
      - Memorial in Two Parts for Violin and Piano, 1988 (Box 43)
      - Octet for Flute, Oboe, Bb Clarinet, Violin, Cello, Percussion and 2 Keyboard Players (Piano, Harpsichord, Celesta, Music Boxes), 1971 (Box 58)
      - Rip for Trumpet, Horn, Trombone and Tape, 1970 (Box 43)
      - Septet for 5 instruments, piano, and speaker/singer, 1969 (Box 43)
      - Soliloquies: Flute (Piccolo, Alto Flute), Clarinet (Bass Clarinet), Violin, Piano (, 1965 (Box 43)
      - Variations for bassoon, voice and percussion (2 players) (text by Howard Nemerov), 1964 (Box 43)
    - Segar, Henry
      - Macbeth for orchestra, 1993 (Box 58)
    - Shrude, Marilyn
      - Passage of Years for Orchestra, 1987 (Box 43)
    - Sloan, Donald
      - Mobiles and Immobiles for solo piano, undated (Box 43)
      - Psalm 130 for mixed choir and four clarinets, undated (Box 43)
      - Tributaries for Piano Quartet, 1993 (Box 43)
    - Smith, Timothy John (student)
      - Bird in Flight: Romance for Cello and Orchestra, undated (Box 43)
      - Out of Darkness: Symphonic Tone Poem in Four Parts undated (Box 43)
    - Somers, Steven
      - Dithyramb for piano, copyright, 1987 (Box 43)
      - Sketches for Chamber Orchestra, copyright, 1986 (Box 43)
    - Sosin, Donald
      - Esther for voice and piano copyright, 1977 (Box 43)
        (includes clippings)
      - Four Evening Songs for mezzo-soprano, flute, clarinet, harp, harmonium, viola, cello, 1973 (Box 53)
    - Sparr, DJ
      - Wrought Hocket for orchestra, 1997 (Box 53)
    - Spring, Glenn
      - Petite Suite for Violin, Cello, and Piano, copyright, 1989 (Box 43)
      - Contrasts for organ, copyright, 1986 (Box 43)
      - Masques for oboe, clarinet and viola, copyright, 1983 (Box 43)
    - Starr, Alana (student)
      - Amin Prelude a Miranda for piano, undated (Box 43)
      - Nate for piano, undated (Box 43)
      - Untitled saxophone quartet undated (Box 43)
    - Stiller, Andrew
      - The Water is Wide, Daisy Bell for piano solo, 1987 (Box 43)
    - Stockhausen, Karlheinz
      - Klavierstucke V and VI, undated (Box 43)
      - Nr. 6 Gruppen fur drei Orchester, 1957 (Box 43)
      - Nr. 12 Kontakte undated (Box 53)
      - Spiral for One Soloist 1968 (Box 43)
    - Stover, Harold
      - Counting the Mad: Music for baritone voice and piano (text by Donald Justice), 1968 (Box 44)
      - Two Pieces for Two Harpsichords, 1979 (Box 44)
    - Strawinsky, Igor. Thereni (Box 44)
    - Thorne, Nicholas (Box 44)
    - Publicity brochure undated
      - From the Dying Earth: Three Tales for Eleven Players 1980 (Box 53)
      - Revelations for orchestra, 1987 (Box 44)
      - Summer's Saraband: Quartet for Clarinet, Violin, Violoncello, and Piano, 1986 (Box 44)
      - Three Love Songs for piano 1980 (Box 44)
      - Three Tales, Book 3: The Visionary New World, 1983 (Box 44)
    - Ticheli, Frank
      - Gaian Visions for concert band, 1990 (Box 44)
    - Tipei, Sever (student)
      - Cuniculi for five tubas, 1986 (Box 44)
    - Toensing, Richard
      - Hidden Ground for Piano, 1979 (Box 44)
      - Homage to David Smith for Organ and Bell Plate 1980 (Box 44)
    - Troxell, Jerry J.
      - Prayers of Steel for Mixed Voices a cappella (text by Carl Sandburg), copyright, 1992 (Box 44)
      - Time Tree--Pitch Tree: A fantasy for Clarinet, Soprano and Audience, copyright, 1976 (Box 54)
    - Vaillancourt, Scott
      - Windfall for orchestra, 1994 (Box 54)
    - Van Buren, John
      - Orgelfantasie 1980 (Box 44)
        (includes note from composer and biographical material)
    - Van Domselaer, Jakob
      - Proeven Van Stijlkunst voor klavier, 1916 (Box 44)
    - Van Duzen, Cheryl (student)
      - A Chinese Proverb for voices, undated (Box 44)
      - Diablo, undated (Box 44)
      - Psalm 150 for voices and piano, undated (Box 44)
      - Snowball Effect, undated (Box 44)
    - Vayo, David (student)
      - Prayer: In Memoriam Olivier Messiaen, for organ, 1992 (Box 44)
      - Symphony: Blossoms and Awakenings for Orchestra 1990 (Box 54)
      - Wings for cello and piano, 1993 (Box 44)
    - Warner, Scott Alan (student)
      - American Dances for String Quartet, copyright, 1994 (Box 44)
      - Golden Heart (chamber symphony), 1993 (Box 44)
      - Songs of Walt Whitman for mixed chorus, copyright, 1994 (Box 44)
    - Weiss, Herman
      - Associations for Piano Solo, 1968 (Box 44)
      - Cantata: Men are not Free for Mezzo-Soprano (or Baritone) voice, Clarinet, Violin, and Viola (text by Kenneth Patchen), 1970[?] (Box 44)
    - Wells, Thomas
      - Concerto for Piano and Chamber Orchestra, undated (Box 44)
      - Three Songs on poems of T.S. Eliot: Mezzo Soprano, Piano, copyright, 1994 (Box 44)
    - Welsh, Wilmer Hayden
      - Songs of the Seasons: A Cycle of Four Songs for High Voice and Piano, undated (Box 44)
    - Wienhorst, Richard
      - Mirrors for piano, copyright, 1988 (Box 44)
    - Wiens, Carl
      - Child of the Way For: Voice, Flute, Violin and Violoncello, 1991 (Box 44)
      - Love Songs (text by Anne Sexton)., circa 1993 (Box 44)
        (draft; includes note from composer)
      - O Crux for SSATTB, 1991 (Box 44)
    - Wilding-White, R.
      - Whatzit No.5: A Piano Piece for Peltzer, 1969 (Box 45)
    - Wiley, Frank
      - Premonition for solo organ, copyright, 1976 (Box 45)
    - Wilson, Don
      - Stabile II: a Perpetual Canon for Five or More Players 1965 (Box 45)
    - Winges, Mark
      - Heads, Hands and Feet for two organs, 1987 (Box 45)
      - Winter Canticles for Organ, 1985 (Box 45)
    - Winsor, Phil (friend)
      - Publicity brochures undated (Box 45)
      - Coronation for four amplified trumpets, 1966 (Box 45)
      - Do not Go Gentle into that Good Night for Orchestra, copyright, 1977 (Box 45)
      - Gumbo for Julia: Trio for Soprano, Alto, and Repetophone (an instrument requiring 9 players), 1967 (Box 45)
      - Orgel II for pipe organ and pre-recorded tape, 1968 (Box 45)
      - Piano Etudes, 1996 (Box 45)
      - Planesong for octet (variable instrumentation), 1980 (Box 45)
      - Variations for Piano, 1968 (Box 45)
    - Woolf, Randall
      - White Heat for orchestra, undated (Box 45)
    - Worley, Daniel
      - Against the Night for Orchestra, 1995 (Box 54)
      - Beat...(Primal Invention) for Small Orchestra, 1997 (Box 45)
      - Big Bad for slightly altered Big Band, 1995 (Box 45)
      - From the Age of Fear: String Quartet No. 1, 1994 (Box 45)
      - Incarcerating Raven for Clarinet and Percussion, 1994 (Box 45)
      - No One is Looking for flute, clarinet, trombone, marimba, mezzo soprano, electric guitar and electric bass (text by Michele Kotler), 1997 (Box 45)
      - Tongues for Amplified Chamber Orchestra and Two Female Vocalists (text by Edward Ball), 1996 (Box 45)
      - To Tame the Beast for Alto Saxophone and Piano, 1992 (Box 45)
      - Trilogy (Suite for Three Guitars), 1995 (Box 45)
      - Urban Thoughts: Concerto for Alto Saxophone and Chamber Orchestra, 1996 (Box 45)
      - What am I? A setting of a poem by Walt Whitman for SATB chorus divisi, 1993 (Box 45)
    - Young, Charles Rochester
      - Saxophone Quartet in Three Movements, 1988 (Box 45)
    - Youtz, Gregory (student)
      - Fire Works for concert band, undated (Box 46)
      - If We Sell You Our Land: For mixed choir, piccolo, flute, alto flute (one player) and percussion, circa 1987 (Box 46)
      - The Window Between: A symphony in four movements for mezzo-soprano and orchestra, 1986 (Box 46)
    - Zajonc, Michael
      - Rondo for Violin and Piano, 1992 (Box 46)
    - Ziporyn, Evan
      - Pleasureville, Pain City for orchestra, 1985 (Box 46)
      - Tree Frog for violin, electric guitar, trombone, bass clarinet, baritone saxophone, percussion and keyboard, copyright, 1993 (Box 46)
      - Waiting by the Phone for solo clarinet in Bb, copyright, 1986 (Box 46)
      - What She Saw There for cello and marimba, 1989 (Box 46)
    - Unidentified
      - Descension for alto saxophone, trumpet, tenor sax and bass clarinet, undated (Box 58)
      - Do It! (incomplete), 1973 (Box 46)
      - Untitled for orchestra undated (Box 54)
        (includes notes by W.A.)
    - Various Composers
      - For Glenn Watkins: Tributes by Composers on the occasion of his retirement from the faculty of the University of Michigan School of Music 1996
        (includes research and notes)
        - William Albright A Post-modern Foxtrot on "Moro lasso" and "Vissi d'arte" for piano left hand (and arm) (Box 46)
        - David Asplin Harmony and Order for choir SSATB (Box 46)
        - Leslie Bassett Two Trio Inventions for three cellos (Box 46)
        - Derek Bermel Old Ones for voice and piano (Box 46)
        - William Bolcom Au revoir, G.E.W. for bass marimba (2 players) (Box 46)
        - Evan Chambers Meditation for two violas (Box 46)
        - Paul Cooper Frescoes for solo piano (Box 46)
        - Michael Daugherty Egyptian Time for solo voice and piano (Box 46)
        - Jacques Desjardins Un Phare a l'horizon... for solo trumpet (Box 46)
        - Sydney Hodkinson Thread for solo violin (Box 46)
        - Andrew Mead Prelude for flute, clarinet, violin, and cello (Box 46)
        - Stephen Newby His Eye is on the Sparrow for solo voice (Box 46)
        - Stephen Rush Jex-ings for solo piano (Box 46)
        - Stuart Sankey Canzona for four cellos (Box 46)
        - Bright Sheng A Tune from Childhood for solo clarinet (Box 46)
        - Geoff Stanton Monogram for solo piano (Box 46)
        - George Balch Wilson A One Liner for solo violin (Box 46)
- Recordings
  In the series Recordings (22 boxes), the recordings are listed alphabetically--by song title in the sub-series William Albright Works, by album title in the sub-series Compact Discs and Long-Playing Albums, by type of music (e.g. keyboard or carillon, or works by other composers) in William Albright Performances, by title in William Albright Lectures, and by composer or performer in Other Composers/Performers. There are three media contained in the sub-series William Albright Works and Other Composers/Performers: audiocassettes, Digital Audio Tapes (DATs), and reels (5", 7", and 10 1/2"). The reels are boxed separately from the audiocassettes and DATs.
  Many of the audiocassettes and reels contain several works; sometimes by different composers. Of course, each audiocassette or reel can only be physically located in one place, so one audiocassette or reel may be referenced several times, under different titles. Here is an example of an entry:
  Some of the reels--both Albright works and those of other composers/performers--arrived at the Bentley Historical Library in 1999 contaminated with mold. These have been fumigated. After fumigation, the reels were reboxed, and the labels on the original boxes transcribed on a slip of paper and inserted into the new box with the reel. They have been boxed separately from the rest of the collection (in Boxes 78-81) as a precautionary measure. Though housed separately, the container list reflects the intellectual arrangement.
  - William Albright Works
    - Abiding Passions for Woodwind Quintet
      - [version 1], 1 audiocassettes (Box 59)
      - [version 2], 1 audiocassettes (Box 59)
      - [version 3], 1 audiocassettes (Box 59)
        (taped with Chasm: Symphonic Fragment)
    - A.G.O. Fight Song
      (see also Flights of Fancy: Ballet for Organ)
      - [version 1], 1 audiocassettes (Box 59)
      - [version 2], 1 audiocassettes (Box 59)
        (taped with Bacchanal)
    - An Alleluia Super-Round for Eight or more Singers (similar or mixed voices) and Instruments (optional)
      - [version 1], 2 audiocassettes (Box 59)
      - [version 2], 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 78)
      - [version 3], 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 70)
        (taped with IP&RC)
      - [version 4], 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 70)
        (taped with Seven Deadly Sins)
      - [version 5], 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 79)
        (taped with King of Instruments)
    - Alliance for Orchestra: A dissertation submitted in partial fulfillment of the requirements for the degree of Doctor of Musical Arts (Music: Composition) in the University of Michigan, 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 69)
    - Amerithon: For solo dancer, any number of instruments, tape (optional), film, projections, and revolving masterworks of art
      - [version 1], 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 69)
        (taped with Alliance)
      - [version 2], 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 69)
        (taped with Father We Thank Thee)
    - Antigone's Reply (Sophocles)
      - [version 1], 1 audiocassettes (Box 59)
      - [version 2], 1 audiocassettes (Box 59)
        (taped with Alleluia)
      - [version 3], 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 69)
    - Bacchanal for Organ Solo and Orchestra
      - [versions 1-4], 4 audiocassettes (Box 59)
      - [version 5], 1 audiocassettes (Box 59)
        (taped with Doo-Dah)
      - [versions 6-7], 2 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 69)
      - [versions 8-9], 2 reel-to-reel audiotapes 5" (Box 69)
      - [version 10], 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 78)
    - Beulahland Rag
      - [versions 1-3], 3 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 69)
      - [version 4], 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 5" (Box 69)
      - [version 5], 3 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 78)
    - The Birth of Jesus/Alleluia for treble voices (SA) and organ with optional mixed choir (SATB) and optional Bells, 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 71)
      (taped with Shadows)
    - Brass Knuckles, 1 audiocassettes (Box 59)
    - Brass Tacks--Ragtime March
      - [versions 1-2], 2 audiocassettes (Box 59)
    - Caroms for Eight Players
      - [version 1], 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 69)
      - [versions 2-4], 3 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 78)
      - [version 5], 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 70)
      - [version 6], 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 70)
        (taped with Pianoagogo)
      - [version 7], 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 70)
        (taped with Saints Preserve Us)
      - [version 8], 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 70)
      - [version 9], 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 79)
        (taped with Stipendium Peccati)
    - Chasm for pipe organ (with optional "echo" instrument
      - [version 1], 1 audiocassettes (Box 59)
      - [version 2], 1 audiocassettes (Box 59)
    - Chasm: Symphonic Fragment
      - [versions 1-3], 3 audiocassettes (Box 59)
    - Chichester Mass: mixed choir a cappella
      - [versions 1-4], 4 audiocassettes (Box 59)
      - [version 5], 1 audiocassettes (Box 59)
      - [version 6], 1 audiocassettes (Box 59)
      - [version 7], 1 audiocassettes (Box 59)
        (taped with Four Fancies)
      - [version 8], 1 audiocassettes (Box 60)
        (taped with Gothic Suite)
      - [version 9], 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 78)
      - [version 10], 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 69)
        (taped with Five Chromatic Dances)
      - [version 11], 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 70)
      - [version 12], 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 70)
      - [version 13], 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 78)
    - Concerto for Harpsichord and String Orchestra
      - [versions 1-6], 6 audiocassettes (Box 59)
      - [version 7], 1 audiocassettes digital audio tapes (Box 59)
    - Cross of Gold: music-theater for actors, choir and musicians
      - [version 1], 1 audiocassettes (Box 59)
      - [version 2], 4 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 69)
    - Danse Macabre
      - [version 1], 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 5" (Box 69)
      - [version 2], 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 78)
      - [version 3], 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 70)
        (taped with Marginal Worlds)
      - [version 4], 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 70)
      - [version 5], 2 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 70)
    - David's Songs, for SATB (soloists or chorus) and organ
      - [versions 1-6], 6 audiocassettes (Box 59)
      - [version 7], 1 audiocassettes (Box 59)
        (taped with Chichester Mass)
      - [version 8], 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 69)
        (taped with Cross of Gold)
    - Daydream
      - [version 1], 1 audiocassettes (Box 59)
      - [version 2], 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 78)
    - De Spiritum, organ solo with 2 assistants
      - [version 1], 2 audiocassettes (Box 59)
      - [version 2], 1 audiocassettes (Box 59)
    - Deo Gratias: arrangement for voice and 5 players, 1 audiocassettes (Box 59)
    - Deum de Deo: A trilogy of pieces for mixed chorus with organ or piano accompaniment
      - [version 1], 2 audiocassettes (Box 59)
      - [version 2], 1 audiocassettes (Box 59)
    - Dona Nobis Pacem, for mixed chorus and piano
      - [version 1-2], 2 audiocassettes (Box 59)
      - [version 3], 1 audiocassettes (Box 59)
    - Doo-Dah, for 3 alto saxophones
      - [version 1], 8 audiocassettes (Box 59)
      - [version 2], 4 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 69)
      - [version 3], 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 78)
      - [version 4], 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 70)
    - Dream and Dance, for organ and percussion
      - [version 1], 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 69)